University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Interviews Collection 1984.0025
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Peoples of Connecticut, 1973-1976
  - Italian Interviews
    - Excellente, Leonard (45 pp.), 1974 December 2; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Excelente (Box 51, Folder Excellente: [39153013993284])
    - Falcigno, Teresa (26 pp.), 1975 March 20; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Falcigno (Box 51, Folder Falcigno: [39153013993292])
    - Farr, Filomena (22 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Farr (Box 51, Folder Farr: [39153013993300])
    - Favretti, Giovanni (Mrs.) (23 pp.), 1975 February 4; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Favretti (Box 51, Folder Favretti: [39153013993318])
    - Frasca, Joseph (21 pp.), 1975 December 19; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Frasca (Box 51, Folder Frasca Joseph: [39153013993326])
    - Frasca, Maria (28 pp.), 1974 December 12; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Frasca_M (Box 51, Folder Frasca Maria: [39153013993334])
    - Frassinelli, Attilio (45 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Frassinelli (Box 51, Folder Frassinelli: [39153013993342])
    - Giorgio, Carl and Theresa (57 pp.), 1975 January 18; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Giorgio (Box 51, Folder Giorgio: [39153013993359])
    - Guida, Bartholemew (Mayor) (30 pp.), 1975 January 21; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Guida (Box 52, Folder Guida: [39153013993375])
    - Laudano, Peter (Mr. and Mrs.) (51 pp.), 1975 April 10; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Laudano (Box 52, Folder Laudano: [39153013993383])
    - Matera, Sarino (7 pp.), 1974 November 18; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Matera (Box 52, Folder Matera: [39153013993391])
    - Pascale, Ralph (34 pp.), 1975 July 27; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Pascale (Box 52, Folder Pascale: [39153013993409])
    - Pelliccio, Nicolas (81 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Pelliccio (Box 52, Folder Pelliccio: [39153013993417])
    - Pezze, Angelo (34 pp.), 1975 June 20; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Pezze (Box 52, Folder Pezze: [39153013993425])
    - Pioppi, Isabella (31 pp.), 1975 June 17; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Pioppi (Box 52, Folder Pioppi: [39153013993433])
    - Pola, Luigi (27 pp.)
    - Polo, Carmine (22 pp.), 1974 September 23; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Polo (Box 52, Folder Polo: [39153013993441])
    - Randazzo, Ernest (Mrs.) (50 pp.), 1975 April 12; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Randazzo (Box 52, Folder Randazzo: [39153013993458])
    - Riccio family (48 pp.), 1974 October 18; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Riccio (Box 52, Folder Riccio: [39153013993466])
    - Russo, Michael (66 pp.), 1974 March 3; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Russo (Box 52, Folder Russo: [39153013993474])
    - Servidone (Mrs.) (6 p.), 1974 December 1; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Servidone (Box 52, Folder Servidone Mrs: [39153013993482])
    - Servidone, Rose (21 pp.), 1974 November 14; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Servidone_R (Box 52, Folder Servidone Rose: [39153013993490])
    - Sidoli, Louis (41 pp.), 1974 September 30; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Sidoli (Box 52, Folder Sidoli: [39153013993508])
    - Tapogna, Anthony (25 pp.), 1975 March 22; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Italian/Tapogna (Box 52, Folder Tapogna: [39153013993516])
  - Jewish Interviews
    - Feldman, Abraham, Rabbi (22 pp.), 1974 October 21; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Feldman (Box 53, Folder Feldman: [39153013993557])
    - Flaks, Abraham (17 pp.), 1975 May 23; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Flaks (Box 53, Folder Flaks: [39153013993565])
    - Gershman, Harry and Minnie (37 pp.), 1974 November 4; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Gershman (Box 53, Folder Gershman: [39153013993540])
    - Golden, Ira and Gertrude (21 pp.), 1975 April 29 (Box 53, Folder Golden: [39153013993573])
    - Goodwin, Paul (23 pp.), 1975 April 11; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Goodwin_P (Box 53, Folder Goodwin Paul: [39153013993599])
    - Goodwin, Louis (23 pp.), 1975 April 11; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Goodwin (Box 53, Folder Goodwin Louis: [39153013993607])
    - Gordon, Mollie (35 pp.), 1974 April 9; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Gordon (Box 53, Folder Gordon: [39153013993615])
    - Kaplan, Benjamin (31 pp.), 1975 February 16; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Kaplan (Box 53, Folder Kaplan: [39153013993623])
    - Lear, Maxwell (29 pp.), 1974 October 14; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Lear (Box 53, Folder Lear: [39153013993631])
    - Leeraar, Jack (25 pp.), 1975 July 17; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Leeraar (Box 53, Folder Leeraar: [39153013993649])
    - Nathanson, Joseph (31 pp.), 1975 April 28; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Nathanson (Box 53, Folder Nathanson: [39153013993656])
    - Neiditz, Moses (20 pp.), 1974 November 11; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Neiditz (Box 53, Folder Neiditz: [39153013993664])
    - Pregozen, Marcia and Harry (24 pp.), 1975 April 25; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Pregozen (Box 53, Folder Pregozen: [39153013993672])
    - Rosenthal, Simon (13 pp.), 1975 May 14; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Rosenthal (Box 53, Folder Rosenthal: [39153013993680])
    - Spector, Isaiah (62 pp.), 1974 December 5; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Spector (Box 53, Folder Spector: [39153013993698])
    - Steinberg, Michael (39 pp.), 1975 July 7; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Jewish/Steinberg (Box 53, Folder Steinberg: [39153013993706])
  - Polish Interviews
    - Blecharczyk, Louis, Msgr. (32 pp.), 1975 June 3; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Blecharczyk (Box 54, Folder Blecharczyk: [39153013993714])
    - Choromanski, Frederick (11 pp.), 1975 April 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Choromanski (Box 54, Folder Choromanski: [39153013994993])
    - Dulka, Joseph (29 pp.), 1974 November 30; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Dulka (Box 54, Folder Dulka: [39153013994985])
    - Hudak, Eva (39 pp.), 1975 April 12; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Hudak (Box 54, Folder Hudak: [39153013994977])
    - Luftglas, Roman (31 pp.), 1974 December 3; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Luftglas (Box 54, Folder Luftglas: [39153013994969])
    - Macknik, Charles (25 pp.), 1975 January 20; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Macknik (Box 54, Folder Macknik: [39153013994951])
    - Markiewicz, Edmund (23 pp.), 1974 October 19; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Markiewicz (Box 54, Folder Markiewicz: [39153013994944])
    - Mierzwinski, Theophil, Rev. (23 pp.), 1975 January 15; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Mierzwinski (Box 54, Folder Mierzwinski: [39153013994936])
    - Oles, John S. (46 pp.), 1975 January 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Oles (Box 54, Folder Oles: [39153013994928])
    - Sangailo, Anna (13 pp.), 1974 December 2; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Sangailo (Box 54, Folder Sangailo: [39153013994910])
    - Sclafani, Bernice (19 pp.), 1975 May 12; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Sclafani (Box 54, Folder Sclafani: [39153013994902])
    - Wodarski, John P., Msgr. (27 pp.), 1975 January 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/Polish/Wodarski (Box 54, Folder Wodarski: [39153013994894])
  - Puerto-Rican Interviews
    - Alvarez, Sepho (10 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Alvarez (Box 55, Folder Alvarez: [39153013994886])
    - Cordero, Louis Perez (18 pp.), 1975 February 13; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Cordero (Box 55, Folder Cordero: [39153013994878])
    - Del Rio, Gumersindo (36 pp.), 1975 August 8; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/DelRio (Box 55, Folder Del Rio: [39153013994860])
    - Echevaria, Francisco (28 pp.), 1975 January 28; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Echevaria (Box 55, Folder Echevaria: [39153013994696])
    - Figueroa, Marilyn (16 pp.), 1975 February 6; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Figueroa (Box 55, Folder Figueroa: [39153013994704])
    - Maldanado, Daniel (28 pp.), 1975 April 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Maldanado (Box 55, Folder Maldanado: [39153013994712])
    - Marques (Mrs.) (14 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Marques (Box 55, Folder Marques: [39153013994720])
    - Rivera, Marina (53 pp.), 1975 April 29; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Rivera (Box 55, Folder Rivera: [39153013994738])
    - Velis, Pura (40 pp.), 1975 August 3; 1984-0025/PeoplesofCT/PuertoRican/Velis (Box 55, Folder Velis: [39153013994746])
  - Miscellaneous Interviews
    - George Baumann (German) (10 pp.)
    - Ingrid Bronner (Norwegian) (31 pp.)
    - W. Gina (Ukranian) (36 pp.)
    - Pauline Hutchinson (Yankee) (19 pp.)
    - Philip Johnson (Yankee) (31 pp.)
    - Msgr. Francis Juras (Lithuanian) (24 pp.)
    - John Kasparian (Armenian) (27 pp.)
    - Carl Malmberg (Swedish) (27 pp.)
    - Doris Hall McBee (Yankee) (29 pp.)
    - Geraldine Novotny (Czech) (28 pp.)
    - Marion Pardus (Czech) (27 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_7e07f6452cd228f140a1857d36007c24)
- The Political Activities Of The First Generation Of Fully Enfranchised Connecticut Women, 1920-1945, 1980-1982 (Box 57, Box 58)
  - Biglow, Marian Y. (50 pp.), 1980 June 16 (Box 57, Folder 1 [39153030466876])
  - Blood, Virginia L. (56 pp.), 1980 August 7 (Box 57, Folder 2 [39153030466884])
  - Brown, Emily Sophie (46 pp.), 1980 July 1 (Box 57, Folder 3 [39153030466892])
  - Bryant, Josephine E. (37 pp.), 1980 July 18 (Box 57, Folder 4 [39153030466900])
  - Cook, Edith Valet (37 pp.), 1982 January 4 (Box 57, Folder 5 [39153030466918])
  - Dadourian, Ruth Mcintyre (65 pp.), 1980 June 30 (Box 57, Folder 6 [39153030466926])
  - Green, Helen A. (38 pp.), 1980 June 23 (Box 57, Folder 7 [39153030466934])
  - Kamenski, Stephanie (37 pp.), 1980 August 14 (Box 57, Folder 8 [39153030466942])
  - Kitchel, Helen Binney (75 pp.), 1980 July 17 (Box 57, Folder 9 [39153030466959])
  - Lee, Percy Maxim (70 pp.), 1980 July 14 (Box 57, Folder 10 [39153030466983])
  - Little, Eleanor H. (74 pp.), 1980 June 11 (Box 57, Folder 11 [39153030466991])
  - McCoy, Laura Belle Reed (70 pp.), 1980 July 30 (Box 57, Folder 12 [39153030467007])
  - Morrison, Margaret Nordhoff (113 pp.), 1981 March 26 (Box 57, Folder 13 [39153030467015])
  - Parmelee, Alice Emmons (59 pp.), 1980 June 24 (Box 58, Folder 1 [39153030467023])
  - Purtell, Edna Mary (62 pp.), 1980 June 18 - July 8 (Box 58, Folder 2 [39153030467031])
  - Rockefeller, Nancy Carnegie (54 pp.), 1981 February 1 (Box 58, Folder 3 [39153030467049])
  - Rostow, Celia Duhan (53 pp.), 1980 July 16 (Box 58, Folder 4 [39153030467056])
  - Rylander, Isabel Curtin (48 pp.), 1980 July 24 (Box 58, Folder 5 [39153030467064])
  - Standish, Hilda Crosby (58 pp.), 1980 July 28 (Box 58, Folder 6 [39153030467072])
  - Sullivan, Hazel Thrall (44 pp.), 1980 August 14 (Box 58, Folder 7 [39153030467106])
  - Woodhouse, Chase Going (85 pp.), 1981 January 31 (Box 58, Folder 8 [39153030467114])
- Red Brick in the Land of Steady Habits, 2002-2004 (Box 59)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Bruce Stave. Interviews by Bruce Stave. This project was conducted as research for the creation of a University history in commemoration of the institution's 125th anniversary. The interviews took place between 2002-2004 and the book published in 2006.]
  - Brohinsky, Scott (60 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_194af6499c6c7a51ae64acf442b63d93)
  - Fox, Karla (66 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_42d97e50e67e20dc071d50fb781afbd8)
  - Potterton, Barbara Isham (37 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_fe09a04684b9ab0e1e90a04c67d33ec0)
  - Rogers, Alfred; Blume, Daniel; Lapuk, Marvin (65 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_4736a604473f538aa79bf4f9c6b8e85e)
  - Rohrbach, John (40 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_472667c9475dd17191a5a86eef57f8a6)
  - Tenzer, Morton (88 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_9f07bc9932dfc3e21852600a1017e1de)
  - Wiggins, Carol A. (72 pp.) (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_41aed57482c2ae6a1a0838b6d69e9c62)
  - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_88cc002375bbdc10d7f26c87d5c68e57)
- Southern New England Telephone Company, 1999 (Box 61)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave and John Sutherland.]
  - Robert Archambault (44 pp.)
  - Barry M. Bloom (26 pp.)
  - Madelyn M. DeMatteo (48 pp.)
  - Paul Dunn (69 pp.)
  - Richard S. Eckstrom (39 pp.)
  - Jean Handley (38 pp.)
  - Maria Teresa Lombardi (Terry Gomez) (48 pp.)
  - Mary Mecagni (40 pp.)
  - Clara Melia (38 pp.)
  - Daniel J. Miglio (49 pp., portions restricted until 6/2019)
  - Walter Monteith (30 pp.)
  - Philip Paolella (30 pp.)
  - Robert J. Patterson (46 pp.)
  - Russell Sullivan (31 pp.)
  - Francis B. Yates (40 pp.)
  - Frank E. Wollanstock (40 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_134f9dc48596639a0ca3c5d09c596a2e)
- Student Projects, undated, 1981-1998 (Box 62)
  - unspecified
    [Interviews By: Amy Garfinkle, 1981, on public history.]
    - Robert Claus (15 pp.)
    - Bruce Fraser (45 pp.)
    - Judith Lohman (23 pp.)
    - Marsh Russo (19 pp.)
    - Floyd Shumway (27 pp.)
    - Clark Strickland (32 pp.)
  - unspecified
    [Interviews By: Lisbeth H. Dizney, 1996-1997. Interviews Women in the Connecticut Legislature: Past and Present. See also: Interviews listed under Connecticut General Assembly and Creating Connecticut's Modern General Assembly.]
    - Susan Barret (9 pp.)
    - Julie Belaga (6 pp.)
    - Susan Bysiewicz (5 pp.)
    - Thomasina Clemons (6 pp.)
    - Jackie Coco (6 pp.)
    - Ann Dandrow (4 pp.)
    - Jackie Durrel (12 pp.)
    - Mary Eberle (4 pp.)
    - Ruth Fahrbach (4 pp.)
    - Jenny Garvey (4 pp.)
    - Sonny Googins (5 pp.)
    - Elaine Hammers (7 pp.)
    - Denise Merrill (28 pp.)
    - Alice Meyers (7 pp.)
    - Dorothy Miller (8 pp.)
    - Dolly Powers (10 pp.)
    - Jodi Rell (5 pp.)
    - Pamela Sawyer (12 pp.)
    - Lee Scarpetti (5 pp.)
    - Eleanor Wilbur (9 pp.)
  - unspecified
    [Interviews By: Sarah Matters, 1998, Connecticut Vietnam War Veterans. See also: Individual Interviews-Vietnam Veterans]
    - Samuel B. Bromley (11 pp.)
    - James M. Brodowski, Sr. (45 pp.)
    - Andrew Carey, III (31 pp.)
    - George W. Chaput (28 pp.)
    - Ronald R. Chaput (22 pp.)
    - William Csere (23 pp.)
    - James F. Kendall (6 pp.)
    - Stanley M. Lucas (18 pp.)
    - Henry J. Madamba (24 pp.)
    - Gerald W. Minikowski (42 pp.)
    - Richard Palmer (13 pp.)
    - Gary Allen Weller (33 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_262595e112957a316ec5fc429395e027)
- Telling Our Stories: Women's Words/Women's Quilts, 1991-1992 (Box 63)
  - [Project Director: Michele Palmer. Interviews By: Michele Palmer. A quilt exhibit, "Quilt Connections: An Exhibit and Oral History," was held in conjunction with this project at the Homer Babbidge Library in 1992.]
  - Pat Carter (35 pp.)
  - Camille Forman (47 pp.)
  - Julie Henry (45 pp.)
  - Donna McLaughlin (23 pp.)
  - Vivian Putnam (37 pp.)
  - Ruth Reichel (36 pp.)
  - Janice Sargent (46 pp.)
  - Cathy Smith (54 pp.)
  - Juanita Thornton (39 pp.)
  - Marilyn Waniek (24 pp.)
- Thomas Dodd Family Oral History Project, 1976, 1995, 2009-2010 (Box 65, Box 66)
  - [Interviews By: Michele Palmer, Robert McMahon and Bruce M. Stave.]
  - Dingell, John D., Jr. (20 pp.), 2010; 1984-0025/DoddFamily/Dingell
    Oral histories (document genres); Dodd, Thomas J. (Thomas Joseph)
  - Christopher Dodd (1976, 42 pp.)
  - Mary Dwyer (1995, 47pp.)
  - Helen Farley (1995, 38pp.)
  - Inouye, Daniel (21pp.), 2010; 1984-0025/DoddFamily/Inouye
  - Israelite, Stanley (35pp.), 2009; 1984-0025/DoddFamily/Israelite
  - Stanley Israelite, 1969-2011 (Box 1)
    File contains optical disks: a CD labeled "Stanley Israelite Disk" and a DVD titled "The Stanley Israelite Story" and a CD labeled "Howard Sacks Sacks Final Transcript"; Photocopies: signed "Interviewee Permission Form", "Interviewee Agreement of Consent", photocopies of correspondence, notes, and articles; Publications: print-outs of internet articles about Stanley Israelite; Correspondence: emails between interviewers and the interviewee; Notes, Transcript: of the interview of Stanley Israelite, Maps: Mapquest directions from Coventry, CT to Norwich, CT
    Politicians; Oral histories (document genres)
  - Daniel Inouye, 1964-2011 (Box 1)
    Contains: Optical Disks: CD labeled "Dodd OHP, Sen. Daniel Inouye 3 MP3"; Photocopies: "Interviewee Permission Form", "Interviewee Agreement of Consent", articles about Thomas J Dodd, articles about Daniel Inouye; Publications: print-outs of internet articles about Daniel Inouye; Notes: list of questions to ask during interview, other notes; Transcript: of interview of Daniel Inouye, speeches given on the 100th birthday of Thomas J Dodd, Congressional Record of speeches mentioning the dedication of the Thomas J Dodd Research Center, other transcripts of Congressional meetings; Correspondence: Copies of correspondence between Thomas J Dodd and Daniel Inouye, correspondence between Senator Inouye's staff and people working on the Dodd Oral History project.
    Oral histories (document genres); Politicians
  - John D. Dingell, Jr., 2010-2011 (Box 1)
    Contains: Optical Disks: CD labeled "Dodd OHP, Rep. John D. Dingell, Jr 3 MP3"; Correspondence: emails between people working on the Dodd Oral History Project, emails between the Dodd Oral History Project and the office of John D. Dingell, Jr., Business Card of the Press Secretary of John D. Dingell, Jr; Legal Documents: signed "Interviewee Permission Form", "Interviewee Agreement of Consent"; Photocopies: "Interviewee Permission Form", "Interviewee Agreement of Consent"; Transcripts: transcript of interview of John D. Dingell, Jr by Bruce M. Stave and Sondra Astor Stave; Notes: "Question Guidelines for John D. Dingell, Jr", Notes including the phone number of Michael Robbins; Publications: print-outs of internet articles about John D. Dingell, Jr; Clippings: Articles about John D. Dingell (specifically with regards to the 2010 elections),
- University Of Connecticut, 1968-2009 (Box 71, Box 70, Box 72, Box 67, Box 69, Box 68)
  - [Project Director: Morton Tenzer (1968-1978) and Bruce M. Stave (1978-2009). Interviews By: Various. *Note: Part of University of Connecticut Alumni Women Oral History Project by Maria Miro Johnson.]
  - Alcorn, Paul (1972-1974, 125 pp., indexed), 1984-0025/UConn/Alcorn
    Oral histories (document genres); University of Connecticut
  - Austin, Philip E. (317pp.,), 2002-2007; 1984-0025/UConn/Austin
  - Babbidge, Homer D., Jr. (Channel 24 interview, 45 pp.), 1968 November 27; 1984-0025/UConn/Babbidge
    University of Connecticut
  - Bailey, Louise (30 pp.), 2008 May 13; 1984-0025/UConn/Bailey
  - Belden, Robert (1976, 37 pp., indexed)
  - Bishop, Mark (28 pp., indexed), 1974 September 20; 1984-0025/UConn/Bishop
  - Brammel, P. Roy (39 pp.), 1972-1973; 1984-0025/UConn/Brammel
    High schools; Edwin O. Smith High School.
  - Brownell, Samuel (172 pp., indexed), 1970-1971; 1984-0025/UConn/Brownell
  - Brundage, Augustus (275 pp.), 1971; 1984-0025/UConn/Brundage
  - Butler, Francelia (119 pp.), 1996 November 22 - 26; 1984-0025/UConn/Butler
  - Carter, W. Harrison (178 pp.), 1972-1973; 1984-0025/UConn/Carter; Carter, W. Harrison (William Harrison), 1905-1974
  - Carolyn Renshaw Chernak* (1981, 22 pp.)
  - J. Orlean Christian (1972, 66 pp., indexed)
  - Clark, Hugh (86 pp.), 1984 January - February; 1984-0025/UConn/Clark
  - Cunningham, John (48 pp.), 1973 February - July; 1984-0025/UConn/Cunningham
  - Sumner A. Dole (1972, 121 pp., indexed)
  - Don Carlos, Harlan (10 pp., indexed), 1968 July 29; 1984-0025/UConn/DonCarlos
  - Nicholas W. Fenney (1972, 11 pp., indexed)
  - Fultz, Charlotte Dutch (63 pp.), 1976 July 12; 1984-0025/UConn/Fultz
  - Gant, Edward V. (23 pp.), 1972 November 27; 1984-0025/UConn/Gant
    Location of Copies or Alternate Formats
    Also available on audiocassette in the University of Connecticut, Provost's Office Records, 1989-0003/AC1.
  - Girard, Pauline Marie (44 pp.), 1981; 1984-0025/UConn/Girard
  - Dorothy Goodwin (1986-92, 437 pp.)
  - Grace, Alonzo (133 pp., indexed), 1970-1971; 1984-0025/UConn/Grace
  - Graf, Daniel (58 pp.), 1973 May 31; 1984-0025/UConn/Graf
  - Jacoby, Hazel and Hotchkiss, Louise and Alan (37 pp.), 1981 January 28; 1984-0025/UConn/Jacoby-Hotchkiss
  - Jorgensen, Albert N. (120 pp.), 1970 May - August; 1984-0025/UConn/Jorgensen
  - Ruth Knight* (1980, 22 pp.)
  - Babette Lapides Koch* (1981, 20 pp.)
  - Lamson, George H. (Mrs.) (42 pp.), 1972 July 14; 1984-0025/UConn/Lamson
  - Liberman, Alvin (100 pp.), 1988 July 13; 1984-0025/UConn/Liberman
  - Raymond I. Longley (1972-1973, 108 pp., indexed)
  - Jerauld Manter (1970, 75 pp., indexed)
  - Marks, Harry (79 pp.), 1980 March 1; 1984-0025/UConn/Marks
  - Edmund A. Moore (1972, 67 pp.)
  - Moreland, Wallace (40 pp.), 1980 September 16; 1984-0025/UConn/Moreland
  - Abbie Storrs Olds and Raymond Olds (1977, 37 pp., indexed)
  - Owen, Charles, Dr. (107 pp.), 1981 June 3; 1984-0025/UConn/Owen
  - Owens, James Stanley (33 pp., indexed), 1973 January - March; 1984-0025/UConn/Owens
  - Howard Roberts (1992, 11 pp.)
  - Julian Rotter (1988, pp.)
  - Saul, George Brandon (27 pp., indexed), 1978 February 17; 1984-0025/UConn/Saul
    Oral histories (document genres)
  - Schenker, Andre (102 pp., indexed), 1968-1969; 1984-0025/UConn/Schenker
  - Ron Schurin (2007, 47 pp.)
  - Seger, Edward D. (84 pp.), 1986 July - August; 1984-0025/UConn/Seger
  - Slate, William L. (30 pp.), 1971 August 31; 1984-0025/UConn/Slate
  - Mary Costello Stuart* (1980, 23 pp.)
  - Stryker, Mrs. (28 pp.), 1977 January 12; 1984-0025/UConn/Stryker
  - Torrey, G. Safford (274 pp., indexed), 1969 August - October; 1984-0025/UConn/Torrey
  - Waugh, Albert (78 pp.), 1981 February 12, 26; 1984-0025/UConn/Waugh
  - Whitney, Edwina (38 pp.), 1968 December 2; 1984-0025/UConn/Whiteney
  - Carolyn Widmer (1972, 74 pp.)
  - Wilson, Kenneth (187 pp.), 1981 November - 1982 January; 1984-0025/UConn/Wilson
  - Elliot Wolk (1992, 31 pp.)
  - Young, Wilfred B. (110 pp., indexed), 1972-1974; 1984-0025/UConn/Young; Young, Wilfred B.
- Voices From The Second World War: An Oral History, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Box 74)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Various. This oral history project was conducted by one class in the fall of 1999 and continued in the spring 2000 semester as an individual independent study. Additional interviews were added from a class taught in 2001 and by a project conducted by Stephen Showers in 2000. The students sought to document the World War II experience from a variety of perspectives including: veterans, children growing up in the period, women, various ethnic groups, and people on the home front. The interviewees reside primarily in Connecticut. Some interviews contain support materials such as photographs.
    See Also: Leavenworth Family Papers for the oral history of Robert D. Leavenworth. The document discusses Sgt. Robert D. Leavenworth's military service experience - between November 1943 and May 1945 - as a top turret gunner and engineer on a B-24 bomber during WW II. It includes his one year German Prison Camp experience at Stalag Luft IV near the Baltic Sea after his plane was shot down on a bombing raid over marshalling yards near Budapest, Hungary. A substantial portion of the document is devoted to the 600 mile Black Death March which started at the end of January 1945 when the German Prison Camp Commander ordered the prisoners to march West when the Russian troops were nearing the camp from the East. Included also are Bob's strong attitudes toward patriotism and the American flag. Bob died on Good Friday 2007 in Arizona.
  - Russell Baril (43 pp.)
  - Neil H. Beaulieu(23 pp.)
  - Raoul Berger (22 pp.)
  - Thomas R. Bodine(23 pp.)
  - Helen Brill(22 pp.)
  - Frances Cavallaro (61 pp.)
  - Francsco Chipelo(66 pp.)
  - Bill Clark(40 pp.)
  - John Clemente(21 pp.)
  - Bob Conrad(47 pp.)
  - Ted Edgerton (38 pp.)